http://www.all3sports.com/pages/privacy-notice

Swim  Wetsuits   Men's Wetsuits   Women's Wetsuits   Wetsuit Accessories Swim Gear   Swim Accessories   Swim Caps   Training ToolsSwim Etc.   Men's Swimwear   Women's Swimwear   Swimskin   GogglesORCA Men's S7 Triathlon WetsuitORCA Women's S7 Triathlon WetsuitBike  Triathlon BikesRoad BikesAdventure/Gravel BikesCyclocross Bikese-BikesMountain BikesUrban/City BikesKid's BikesBike Accessories   Computers   Lights and LocksBike HydrationBike MaintenanceBike TrainersBike Travel CasesHelmets Power MetersBike Components   Bar Tape/Grips   Brakes/Pads/Rotors   Cassettes/Chains   Cranksets/Bottom Brackets   Derailleurs/Shifters   Electronic Shifting Accessories   Handlebars/Stems/Seatposts   Pedals/Cleats/Accessories   Saddles   Tires/Tubes   Wheels Cycling Apparel   Men's Cycling Apparel   Women's Cycling Apparel   Cycling Gloves   Arm/Leg Warmers   Cycling Jackets/Winter Jerseys   Winter Tights   Socks   Cycling ShoesBike Fitting GuideWAHOO FITNESS KICKR SMART TRAINER 2018 EDITIONRun Running Clothing  Men's Running Apparel  Women's Running  ApparelOrca Speed LacesRun Accessories  Compression  Socks  Shoe Lace Systems  Hydration2XU X-Vent Multisport Tri Singlet - Women'sBodyGlide BODY Anti-Chafe BalmShoe Lace SystemsMen's Apparel Men's Apparel  Men's Triathlon Apparel  Men's Cycling Apparel  Men's Run Apparel  Men's Swim ApparelMen's Compression  Men's CompressionClothing, etc.  Socks  Tights  Hats/Visors  Cycling Gloves  Winter Wear  all3sports GearLouis Garneau Tri Comp Sleeveless Tri TopOrca Core Tri Tank 2018 MenWomen's Apparel Women's Apparel  Women's Triathlon Apparel  Women's Cycling Apparel  Swim SuitsWomen's Compression  Women's CompressionClothing Etc.  Socks  Hats/Visors  Cycling Gloves  Winter Wear  Tights  all3sports GearCoeur Sports Women's Triathlon Shorts 5" InseamBlueseventy PZ4TX+ Swimskin - Women'sGear  Electronics   Bike Computer   GPS Watches   Heart Rate Monitor   Electronic Accessories Eyewear   Tifosi   Smith OpticsGear  Bags  Body/Clothing Care  Books  Lifestyle Accessories  Power Meters  Race Accessories  Recovery Gear  Gifts/ChotchkiesWahoo Fitness ELEMNT Bolt GPS Cycling ComputerWahoo TICKR X Heart Rate MonitorNutrition  BarsElectrolyte MixesGelsRecovery MixesSupplementsChewsInfinit Go FarSkratch Labs Everyday Hydration Mix 1 lb.Infinit Jet FuelClearance CategoriesMen's Apparel ClearanceWomen's Apparel ClearanceAccessories ClearanceComponent ClearanceBike ClearanceWetsuits ClearanceBrandsBlog
My Cart
Close
Home
»
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
all3sports, LLC. takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.
What This Privacy Policy Covers
This policy covers how all3sports, LLC. treats personal information that all3sports, LLC. collects and receives, including information related to your past use of all3sports, LLC. products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that all3sports, LLC. does not own or control, or to people that all3sports, LLC. does not employ or manage. In addition, certain all3sports, LLC. associated companies have their own privacy statements that can be viewed at their respective sites.
Information Collection and Use
all3sports, LLC. may collect personal information when you register on all3sports.com, when you visit all3sports.com pages or the pages of certain all3sports, LLC. partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, billing address, and phone number. Once you register with all3sports, LLC. and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. all3sports, LLC. automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, all3sports.com cookie information, and the page you request. all3sports, LLC. uses information for the following general purposes: to customize your shopping experience, improve our services, contact you, and conduct internal research.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
all3sports, LLC. does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with all3sports, LLC. under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help all3sports, LLC. communicate with you about offers from all3sports, LLC. and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of all3sports, LLC.'s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
We transfer information about you if all3sports, LLC. is acquired by or merged with another company.
Cookies
all3sports, LLC. may set and access all3sports, LLC. cookies on your computer. Cookie information is used solely for creating a more individualized shopping experience for each shopper. Personal information is not stored in the cookie.
Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences
You can edit your all3sports.com Account Information, at any time. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the all3sports.com, such as service announcements and administrative messages. The all3sports.com email specials are sent to all customers, but one may opt-out of receiving them during account creation or anytime after by unsubscribing in their account options, following the unsubscribe link and instructions within the email specials email, or by contacting all3sports.com.
Confidentiality and Security
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
all3sports, LLC. may update this policy without notification and at will. This policy will always be located on all3sports.com for viewing should one need to review policy changes.
Effective Date: November 25, 2004
Hello You!
Enter your email address for stock alerts, discounts, promotions and more!
